# JUAN C. BARRIOS S.

# FRONT END DEVELOPER

# SKILLS PROFESSIONALS

JavaScript
TypeScript
React
Next
Flutter
React Native
Node / Express
GraphQL
Firebase
Git
Jest
Cypress

# SKILLS PERSONALS

Creative
Trustworthy and professional
Organized
Time management
Teamwork
Fast learner
Motivated
Funny

# CONTACT

+58 4121556808 juanbarrios045@gmail.com https://juanbarrios.vercel.app/

## REFERENCES

JUNIOR SÁNCHEZ
Tauros, Developer FullStack

# **PROFILE**

My name is Juan, I'm 21 years old and I'm from Venezuela. I'm very passionate about web development and technology. I dedicate myself completely to everything I do so that it is the best of the best, I'm creative, fun and I assure you that you will like me very much if you meet me.

I'm a Front End Developer with more than three year of work experience. I also have Back End knowledge becoming a FullStack Developer.



# **EXPERIENCE**

#### **TAUROS**

Nov 2019 - Present

Bring the design to the web using React.js, adapting it to various devices and browsers, using the help of APIs to connect the web with various services or systems.

# **FREELANCER**

Sep 2019 - Present

Offer my services to companies or people who need a solution to their problems through web or mobile development.

#### **ACADEMIC COACH**

Jun 2018 - Jun 2020

Teach through extra classes and workshops to help students perform better.

# **EDUCATION**

# SYSTEMS ANALYST

Instituto Universitario de Tecnología para la informatica | 2017 - 2020